A Guide to the Inge Horton Architectural Collection, 1964-1999
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Articles of Women Architects and Other Topics, n.d.
  - Chairing the California Task Force on the History of Women Architects, 1989 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Four Panels for Exhibition of Women's Work, 1991 (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Moving along/Movement and Change in Architecture and Our Lives, 1991 (Box-folder 8:11)
  - The Interface of Planning and Architecture or Urban Design in San Francisco, 1992 (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Talk about the 11. UIFA Conference in Hungary, 1997 (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Women in Architecture, 1998 (Box-folder 8:14)
  - DPR 523 Form on the Potrero Hill Neighborhood House, 1999 (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Young Ladies with T-Squares -Early Women in Architecture at the University of California, 1890-1950 (Box-folder 8:16, Box-folder 8:17)
  - History of the Organization of Women Architects (OWA), 2003 (Box-folder 8:18)
  - Tend and Befriend: The Benefits of Women's Friendship, 2003 (Box-folder 8:19)
  - Ella Castelhun - A Lesser Known Woman Architect, 2005 (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Honor Your Legacy!, 2008 (Box-folder 8:21)
  - a.DOT architects. Doing Other Things, 2010 (Box-folder 8:22)
  - Submittal for BAQ Design Award Competition, 2010 (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Submittal for Stage Two of the Milka Bliznakov Prize, 2010 (Box-folder 8:24)
  - In Memoriam of Milka Tscherneva Bliznakov, 2010 (Box-folder 8:25)
  - OWA Celebrates 40 Years, 2013 (Box-folder 8:26)
  - OWA History: OWA at 40, 2013 (Box-folder 8:27)
  - Julia Morgan's Cohorts in Sonoma County, 2009-2013 (Box-folder 8:28)
  - Articles of Women Architects and Other Topics Index, n.d. (Box-folder 8:29)
  - Supportive Networks of Emily Williams, San Jose's First Woman Architect, 2006 (Box-folder 8:30)
  - Building a Supportive Community - The Example of Emily Williams, a lesser-known woman in architecture, 2006 (Box-folder 8:31)
  - Emily Williams, San Jose's First Woman Architect, 2006 (Box-folder 8:32)
  - Preservation in San Francisco, 1996 (Box-folder 8:33)
  - Index, n.d. (Box-folder 8:34)